Finding Aid for the Elizabeth Vann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- W.P.A.: CORRESPONDENCE, PHOTOGRAPHS AND NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS
  - Correspondence, 1937 - incoming unless designated by () (Box 26)
    - Feb.17 (to Family) with Press Digest. 1937: Feb.16 (Box 26)
    - Feb.28 M. William Murphy (Box 26)
    - Mar.16 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar.20 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar.24 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar.26 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Apr. 7 V.W. 0'Hara (Box 26)
    - May 6 (to Thelma Parkinson) (Box 26)
    - May 10 William H.J. Ely (Box 26)
    - May 20 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - May 26 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - May 27 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - June 5 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - June 9 Mabel Friedlander (Box 26)
    - June 10 Madeline E. Farrington (Box 26)
    - June 17 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - June 18 Madeline E. Farrington Herraine Keller (Box 26)
    - June 22 Madeline E. Farrington (Box 26)
    - June 24 Mabel Friedlander (Box 26)
    - July 19 (to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - July 23 W.A. Kearns (Box 26)
    - Aug. 20 Kenneth Meeker (Box 26)
    - Oct.9 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Oct.28 Anna Easter (Box 26)
    - n.d. Alice T. (Box 26)
    - Nov.10 Alice T. Geoffrey Norman (Box 26)
    - Nov.12 Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - Nov.17 Caulder B. Pennyclear (Box 26)
    - Nov.24 (to Caulder B. Pennyclear) (Box 26)
    - Dec.2 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Dec.14 Robert W. Allan - with communications to branch managers (7) (Box 26)
    - Dec.15 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Dec.17 Burton Kline (Box 26)
    - Dec.22 William H.J. Ely (Box 26)
  - Folder 5: Incoming cards and telegrams (Box 26)
  - Folder 6: Correspondence, 1938 - incoming unless designated by () (Box 26)
    - n.d. (to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - Jan. 3 Mervil E. Haas (to Sara L. Kearns) (Box 26)
    - Jan. 4 Katherine S. Beattie (Box 26)
    - Jan. 5 (to Mrs. Mervil E. Haas) (Box 26)
    - Jan.13 (to Mrs. George T. Beatty) (to Nelson Smith) (Box 26)
    - Jan.14 Nelson C. Smith William H.J. Ely (Box 26)
    - Jan.15 (to Thelma Parkinson) (Box 26)
    - n.d. Frank S. Katzenbach, III (Box 26)
    - Jan.17 William L. Nunn (Box 26)
    - Jan.19 Jacob G. Lipman (Box 26)
    - Jan. 20 (to H.G. St.Clair) (to James Carson) (Box 26)
    - Jan. 21 Izetta Jewell Miller Lewis Compton (Box 26)
    - n.d. Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - n.d. Frank A. March (Box 26)
    - Jan.24 (to Miss Marion E. Patterson) (Box 26)
    - Jan.25 Thelma Parkinson (Box 26)
    - Arthur Noack - with report (Box 26)
    - (to Dr. William E. Nunn) (Box 26)
    - n.d. (to La Spina) (2)memos (Box 26)
    - Jan.28 Mary T. Rouse (Box 26)
    - William L. Nunn (Box 26)
    - (to Arthur Noack) (Box 26)
    - n.d. Helen A. Marvel (Box 26)
    - Feb.l H.W. Wiggin (Box 26)
    - Feb. 3 (to William P. McDermitt) (Box 26)
    - Feb. 7 Arthur S. Hobby (Box 26)
    - (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - (to J. Spencer Smith) (Box 26)
    - Feb.9 (to George W. Needham) (Box 26)
    - Feb.11 J. Spencer Smith (Box 26)
    - Feb.ll Arthur S. Hobby (Box 26)
    - Feb.18 (to Mary T. Norton) (Box 26)
    - Mar. 4 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar. 7 (to Mrs. Charley Tidd Cole) (Box 26)
    - (to Harry Linde) (Box 26)
    - Mar.11 Kathryn B. Greywacz (Box 26)
    - Mar.12 (to Kathryn B. Greywacz) (Box 26)
    - Mar.14 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - Mar.15 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar.20 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar.25 (William H.J. Ely to L.R. Alderman) (Box 26)
    - Mar.28 (to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - Mar.31 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Apr. 6 (G.L. Maxwell to William H.J. Ely) (Box 26)
    - Apr. 8 Charles H. Pearce (Box 26)
    - Apr.11 (F.H. Dryden to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - Apr.12 Leo P. Hogan (Box 26)
    - Apr.13 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Apr.14 (William H.J. Ely to Lewis Compton) (Box 26)
    - Apr.15 (to Lewis Compton) (Box 26)
    - Apr.21 (Ellen S. Woodward to William H.J. Ely) (Box 26)
    - Apr.25 Robert W. Purdy (Box 26)
    - Apr.28 Mary T. Norton (Box 26)
    - Apr.29 (to W.M. Cotton)(2) (Box 26)
    - (to Saidee (Jarrell) & Evelyn) (Box 26)
    - May 2 (to Mary T. Norton) (Box 26)
    - (to Rebecca Barkley) (Box 26)
    - (to Richard P. Scott) (Box 26)
    - (to Robert H. Morrison) (Box 26)
    - May 3 Richard P.T. Scott) (Box 26)
    - May 18 George W. Tomlinson (Box 26)
    - May 21 John A. Millington (Box 26)
    - June 2 (to Mary A. Russell) (Box 26)
    - June 5 Thomas V. Green (Box 26)
    - June 8 (William H.J. Ely to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - June 11 (to Helen L. Davis) (Box 26)
    - June 15 Harlow(?) H. Cope (Box 26)
    - June 16 (to Helen) (Box 26)
    - June 25 (Fredericka Belknap to Mrs. Frances Scales) (Leo R» Etzkorn to Sarah Askew) (Box 26)
    - June 27 (Sarah Askew to Mr. Kay) (Box 26)
    - July 2 (to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - July 6 Sarah Askew (Box 26)
    - July 11 A.R. McFausland (Box 26)
    - July 12 (William H.J. Ely to Fredericka Belknap) (Box 26)
    - July 13 Ellen S. Woodward (Fredericka Belknap to Frances Scales) (Box 26)
    - July 14 (William H.J. Ely to Fredericka Belknap) (Box 26)
    - July 17 Wesley W. Burden (Box 26)
    - July 18 (to Lewis Compton) (Box 26)
    - July 22 Lewis Compton (Box 26)
    - July 26 Robert W. Allan (to John S. Sheldon) (Box 26)
    - Aug.6 John S. Sheldon (Box 26)
    - Aug.19 (to William H.J". Ely) (to Lewis Compton) (Bernice Winser to Henry G. Alsberg) (Box 26)
    - Aug.22 Rose Lerner Perlman (Box 26)
    - Aug.25 William H.J. Ely (Box 26)
    - Aug.29 (to Vera Noon) (Box 26)
    - Aug. 30 (Robert W. Allan to E.B. Erickson) (Box 26)
    - Aug.31 (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Sept.2 (Thomas M. Woodward to Lewis) (Box 26)
    - Sept.5 C.E. Backman (Box 26)
    - Sept.8 Henry G. Alsberg Izetta Jewell Miller (to Lewis Compton) (to Edmond J. Gale) (to Aneita Keating) (Box 26)
    - Sept.9 (to C.E. Backman) (Box 26)
    - Sept.10 Thomas S. Keary (Box 26)
    - Sept.12 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Sept.13 (to William DeBary) (Box 26)
    - Sept.15 Bernice Harris (Box 26)
    - n.d. Charlotte Gaines (Box 26)
    - Sept.26 (to Lewis Compton) (Box 26)
    - Sept.30 (to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - Oct.l (to Lewis Compton) (Box 26)
    - Oct.18 Ellen S. Woodward (Box 26)
    - Oct.19 Robert W. Allan (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Oct.26 Izetta Jewell Miller to Mrs. Charley Tidd W.J. Burke to H.W. Wiggin) Cole) (Box 26)
    - Oct.27 H.W. Wiggin (Box 26)
    - Nov.2 (George R. Swinton to State Dir., Women's & Professional Projects)with poem,"Promise Yourself" (Box 26)
    - Nov.4 Irene Popper (Box 26)
    - Nov.5 Leo P. Hogan (Box 26)
    - Nov.12 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Nov.15 Louise Molinelli (Box 26)
    - Nov.l, Anne M. Maroney Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Nov.19 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Nov.30 Louise Molinelli (Box 26)
    - Dec.l Katharine M. Donaldson (Box 26)
    - Dec.2 Grace E. Mitchell (Box 26)
    - Dec.3 Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - n.d. ? (Box 26)
    - Dec.7 (Viola L. Hutchinson to Henry G. Alsberg) (Box 26)
    - (Robert W. Allan to Vincent J. Murphy) (Box 26)
    - Dec.10 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Dec.13 (Robert W. Allan to Manager, Branch #l\) (Box 26)
    - Dec.20 Verb Amber Gabbert (Box 26)
    - Dec.22 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Dec.27 Ellen S. Woodward (Box 26)
    - Dec.30 (Helen L. Davis to Ellen S. Woodward) (Box 26)
    - 1940:? Ellen S. Woodward (Box 26)
  - Folder 7: Correspondence, 1939 - incoming unless designated by () (Box 26)
    - n.d. Sara V. Ackuman(3) (Box 26)
    - n.d. Mabel a ? (Box 26)
    - Jan.2 (Nelson H. Peppier to Henry G. Alsberg) (Box 26)
    - Jan.9 Izetta Jewell Miller (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Jan.10 Nelson H. Peppier (Box 26)
    - Jan.11 (Robert I. Bischoff to Helen L. Dowd) (Box 26)
    - Jan.13 (Helen L. Dowd to T.E. Lynch) (Box 26)
    - Jan.18 (Helen L. Dowd to Thomas E. Lynch) (Box 26)
    - Jan.20 (Thomas E. Lynch to Helen L. Dowd) (Box 26)
    - Jan.21 Evelyn T. Walker (Box 26)
    - Jan.24 Florence Kerr (Box 26)
    - Jan.26 John H. Smith R.Z. Smith Ellen S. Woodward (Box 26)
    - Jan.31 Mary Steele Financial statement (Box 26)
    - Feb. 7 John Hall (Box 26)
    - Feb.10 Alice L. Bebout (Box 26)
    - Feb.14 Lorene Trainor (Robert W. Allan to Viola L. Hutchinson) (Box 26)
    - n.d. (Arthur Enger)to a group of people in NJ (Box 26)
    - Feb.17 (Robert W. Allan to Izetta Jewell Miller) (Box 26)
    - Feb.23 Rose Lerner Perlman (Box 26)
    - n.d. Elizabeth B. Robbins (Box 26)
    - Apr.l Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Apr.29 Lillian Scilipoli (Box 26)
    - n.d. (to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - May 9 Verb Amber Gabbert (Box 26)
    - May 26 ? (Box 26)
    - July 21 (Hamilton Cross to Mrs. Scales) (Hamilton Cross to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - July 22 (to Mary T. Norton) (to William A. Smathers) (Box 26)
    - July 28 J. Howard Miller (Viola L. Hutchinson to Ronald G. Chessman) (Box 26)
    - Aug. 2 Mildred (Box 26)
    - Aug./f Ronald G. Chessman (Box 26)
    - Aug. 5 Kathleen G. Hopler (Box 26)
    - Aug. 8 Ronald G. Chessman (Box 26)
    - Aug.18 Katherine S. Beattie (Box 26)
    - Sept.27 Molly?, Altier (Box 26)
    - n.d. Amy Knowlton (Box 26)
    - Sept.28 Ethel M. Harlan (Box 26)
    - n.d. (Verb Amber Gabbert to Robert VV. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Dec.20 (to Mary Weber) (Box 26)
    - Dec.25 Florence Kerr (Box 26)
  - Folder 8: Correspondence, 1940 - incoming unless designated by () (Box 26)
    - Jan.18 Herman Coburn Katharine M. Donaldson (Box 26)
    - Apr.9 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Apr.24 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - n.d. Mabel A. Tiffany - with poem (Box 26)
    - June 13 Lewis Compton (Box 26)
    - June 20 Thelma Parkinson (Box 26)
    - June 22 Malvina C. Thompson (Box 26)
    - June 24 Benjamin F. Sheldon (Box 26)
    - June 26 William E. Ohland (Box 26)
    - July 1 (to Thelma Parkinson) (Box 26)
    - July 30 Charlotte Gaines (Box 26)
    - n.d. (to Mrs. Reda-Reina) (Box 26)
    - Aug.l (to Edward W. Hamilton) (Box 26)
    - Oct.23 George M.C. Fowler (Box 26)
    - Oct.24 (to ?) (Box 26)
    - Oct.28 Charles M. Eryeian (Box 26)
    - Nov.l J. Palmer Collins (Box 26)
    - Nov.30 Katharine M. Donaldson (Box 26)
    - Dec.l Lucie Edmondson Hill (Box 26)
    - Dec. 4 Lucie Edmondson Hill (Box 26)
    - Dec.20 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - (to Florence Kerr) (Box 26)
    - Dec.21 B.H. Parsons (Box 26)
    - Dec.? Florence Kerr(2) (Box 26)
    - 1940: Dec.? New Jersey Arts & Crafts Project, W.P.A. (Box 26)
    - 1941: Jan.14 Florence Kerr (Box 26)
  - Folder 9: Correspondence, 1941 - 1947 - incoming unless designated by (Box 26)
    - 1941 (Box 26)
    - Jan.l John Moroso (Box 26)
    - Jan. 17 James Leland Vass (Box 26)
    - Jan.22? Mrs. Eva H. Reda-Reina;. (Box 26)
    - Feb.9 Katharine Halley (Box 26)
    - Feb.17 (to Katharine Halley) (Box 26)
    - Feb.18 (Leo J. Rogers to Justus Higham) (Box 26)
    - Feb.24 (Justus C. Higham to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Mar. 6 Jessie M. Murdock (Box 26)
    - Mar.11 Harold A. Lett (Box 26)
    - Mar.15 Ruth B. Rebbeck (Box 26)
    - Mar.14 James Leland Vass (Box 26)
    - Mar.31 Eva H. Reda-Reina - with receipt for chest of drawers and cradle (Box 26)
    - (Box 26)
    - Apr. 4 Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - Apr. 9 Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - Apr.15 Stanley Beck (Box 26)
    - Apr.23 Mary A. Mahoney (Box 26)
    - Richard K. Warr (Box 26)
    - May 5 Florence Schwartz (Box 26)
    - May 14 Agnes S. Cronin (Box 26)
    - May 15 receipt for work done on chairs (Box 26)
    - May 18 Lorene Pearce (Box 26)
    - n.d. Viola L. Hutchinson - with clipping & newsletter (Box 26)
    - May 19? William DeBary (Box 26)
    - May 20 Katharine Halley (Box 26)
    - June 2 (Viola L. Hutchinson to William DeBary) (Box 26)
    - June 4 Agnes S. Cronin (Box 26)
    - June 10 (to Agnes S. Cronin) (Box 26)
    - June 30 Viola L. Hutchinson Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - July 1 Katharine Halley (Box 26)
    - July 2 Floyd L. Davis (Box 26)
    - William H.J. Ely (Box 26)
    - George L. Kirchgasney ? (Box 26)
    - C.B. Coane ? (Box 26)
    - July 3 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Ethel M. Harlan (Box 26)
    - July 5 Ray A. Glennon (Box 26)
    - July 6 Irene E. Popper (Box 26)
    - July 7 H.W. Wiggin (Box 26)
    - Frederick Rocke(2) (Box 26)
    - July 8 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - July 9 Benjamin Franklin Seldon (Box 26)
    - July 10 Jane W. Papes (Box 26)
    - Jacob M. Klein (Box 26)
    - n.d. Eva H. Reda-Reina (Box 26)
    - July 15 Aneita Keating (Box 26)
    - n.d. Aneita Keating(2) (Box 26)
    - July 17 Florence Kerr (Box 26)
    - July 19 Harry C. Bebbington (Box 26)
    - July 20 George M.C. Fowler (Box 26)
    - July 22 Anna Grant (Box 26)
    - July 27 Lena Anthony Robbins (Box 26)
    - July 31 (Florence Kerr to Robert W. Allan) (Box 26)
    - Aug.4 (to Lorene Trainor) (Box 26)
    - Aug.21 Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - Aug.26 Thelma Parkinson Sharp (Box 26)
    - Oct.23 Kathryn B. Greywacz (Box 26)
    - Nov.7 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - n.d. Catherine Connelly (Box 26)
    - Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
    - Card from a group of people (Box 26)
    - Mrs. William H.J. Ely & Family (Box 26)
    - Harvey & Mary Ely (Box 26)
    - 1942 (Box 26)
    - Feb.13 Viola L. Hutchinson (Box 26)
    - Feb.20 Izetta Jewell Miller (Box 26)
    - Apr.9 Clifford L. Lord (Box 26)
    - Apr.17 George M.C. Fowler (Box 26)
    - Aug.12 Catherine E. Connelly (Box 26)
    - Sept.20 Emma L. Word (Box 26)
    - Oct.16 Marjorie VanNess (Box 26)
    - Dec.13 Benjamin F. Seldon (Box 26)
    - Dec.21 Marie H. O'Rorke (Box 26)
    - 1943 (Box 26)
    - Aug. 6 Wayne T. Cox (Box 26)
    - 1947 (Box 26)
    - Dec.4 Robert W. Allan (Box 26)
  - Folder 10: W.P.A.: Procedures (Box 26)
    - Lists of workers (Box 26)
    - Federal Project No.l - 1937 (Box 26)
    - Music (Box 26)
    - Theater (Box 26)
    - Writers (Box 26)
    - Archives (Box 26)
    - Report of The Women’s and Professional Division at the state-wide Administrative Conference, Asbury Park, NJ, 1938: July (Box 26)
    - Salaries (Box 26)
  - Folder 11: Miscellaneous Publications, 1935-1941 (Box 26)
    - Canning instructions (Box 26)
    - World Center for Women’s Archives (Box 26)
    - The Democratic Digest. Vol.14,No.l, 1937: Jan. See: “W.P.A. and New Jersey’s Unemployed Women” by Elizabeth Vann and other articles about women. (Box 26)
  - Folder 12: W.P.A. Photographs (Box 26)
    - Photographic plate and photo of Elizabeth, 1930s W.P.A. “Burlington Supreme Court Docquet, 1731-1737.” Historical Records Survey of NJ; (3) microfilm negatives. (Box 26)
  - Folder 13: Newspaper Clippings of W.P.A. Workers and Projects (Box 26)
  - Folder 14: Newspaper Clippings about Elizabeth (Box 26)
  - Folder 15: Federal Writers’ Project: Correspondence (Box 26)
    - n.d. (to ?) (Box 26)
    - 1969: Aug.7 (Jerre Mangione to Viola L. Hutchinson) Aug.18 Viola L. Hutchinson Aug.31 Jerre Mangione Sept.27 Jerre Mangione (Box 26)
    - Folder 16: Federal Writers’ Project: Newspaper Clippings (Box 26)
    - Folder 17: C/S Newsletter. 1941: May, July, Aug., Sept. Book presented to Elizabeth by W.P.A. workers (Box 26)
- AN ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE AND CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN THIRD PARTIES, FOUND IN FOLDERS 1-15. FOLDER NUMBER IS INDICATED BY F
  - Ackuman, Sara V. 1939: ?(3) F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ahlbium, Anne S. 1935: Dec.13 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Allan, Robert W.(Deputy State Administrator)1935: Nov.13 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1936: Feb.29; Sept.2 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1937: Mar.26 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - May 20,27 (Box 26)
  - June 17 (Box 26)
  - Dec.14,15 (Box 26)
  - 1938: Mar.31 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - June 17 (Box 26)
  - Dec.14,15 (Box 26)
  - 1938: Mar.31 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - July 26 (Box 26)
  - Aug.30(to E.B. Erickson) (Box 26)
  - Oct.19 (Box 26)
  - Nov.19 (Box 26)
  - Dec.7(Vincent J. Murphy) (Box 26)
  - Dec.13(Mgr., branch #4) (Box 26)
  - Dec.22 (Box 26)
  - 1939: Feb.14(Viola L. F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Feb.l?(Izetta Jewell (Box 26)
  - Apr.l Miller) (Box 26)
  - Dec.l (Box 26)
  - 1940: Apr.9,24 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - July 8 (Box 26)
  - Nov.7 (Box 26)
  - (l)n.d. (Box 26)
  - 1947: Dec.4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Alsberg, Henry G. 1938: Sept.8 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Altier, Molly(?) 1939; ? F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Askew, Sarah B.(Public Library 1935: Dec.ll,14,17,20 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Commissioner, State of NJ) 1936: Feb.?,13,20 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Mar.25 (Box 26)
  - July 21, 2l(Mrs. Patterson) (Box 26)
  - Dec.21,30 (Box 26)
  - 1938: July 6 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - B (Box 26)
  - Backman, c.E. 1938: Sept.5 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Beattie, Katherine S. 1938: Jan. 4 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1939: Aug. 18 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Bebbington, Harry c. 1941: July 19 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Bebout, Alice L. 1939: Feb.10 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Beck, Stanley 1941: Apr.15 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Belknap, Fredericka 1938: June 25(Mrs. F6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Frances Scales) July 13(Frances Scales) (Box 26)
  - Betz, Eva K. 1937: Jan.8 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Biscoff, Robert I. 1939: Jan.ll(Helen L. Dowd) F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Boyd, Albert T.(Asst. Supervisor, W.P.A.NJ)1936: Feb.4 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE AND CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN THIRD PARTIES
  - B
  - Breslin, James A. 1935: Oct.25 F l (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Burden, Wesley w. 1938: July 17 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Burke, W.J. (District Director) 1936: Dec.3(Wm H.J. Ely) F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1938: Oct.26(H.W.Wiggin)F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - C (Box 26)
  - 1938: Oct.26(H.W.Wiggin)F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - C
  - Carter, Letitia Hall(Dir. of Women’s Activities)1935: Dec.12 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Chessman, Ronald G. 1939: Aug.4,8 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Coane(?), C.B. 1941: July 2 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Coburn, Herman 1940: Jan.18 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Collins, J. Palmer 1940: Nov.l F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Compton, Lewis 1936: May 13 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dec.l (Box 26)
  - 1938: Jan.21 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - July 22 (Box 26)
  - 1940: June 13 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 1942: Aug.12 (Box 26)
  - Cope, Harlow H. 1938: May 15 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cox, Wayne T. 1943: Aug.6 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Cronin, Agnes S. 1941: May 14 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - June 4 (Box 26)
  - Cross, Hamilton 1939: July 21(Mrs Scales) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - July 21(Robert W. Allan)
  - D
  - Davis, Floyd L. 1941: July 2 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Helen L. 1938: Dec.30(Ellen S. Woodward) F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - DeBary, William(Bill) 1935: Sept.9 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Donaldson, Katharine M. 1941: 1938: F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1938: Dec.l F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1940: Jan.? Nov.30 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Doscher, John H.(Chm, Democratic County Commissioner of Bergen Co., NJ) 1936: Aug. 24 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dowd, Helen L. 1936: Dec.11 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1939: Jan.13(T.E.Lynch) F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Jan.18(T.E.Lynch) (Box 26)
  - Dryden, F.H. 1938: Apr.11(Izetta Jewell Miller) F 6 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - E (Box 26)
  - Easter, Anna 1937: Oct.28 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Ellis, William J.”Joe”(Commissioner, State of NJ, Dept. of Institutions and Agencies) 1936: Dec.ll F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE AND CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN THIRD PARTIES
  - E (Box 26)
  - Ely, William H.J.(State Administrator) 1936: Jan.14,15 F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Feb.13(Sarah Askew) (Box 26)
  - Mar.3(Collins Denny) (Box 26)
  - Mar.20 (Box 26)
  - May 6 (Box 26)
  - June 25(L.R. Alderman) (Box 26)
  - June 26 (Box 26)
  - Aug.8,28(Janet Haillie) (Box 26)
  - Dec.21(Izetta J. (Dn.d. Miller (1)n.d. (Box 26)
  - 1937: May 10 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Dec.22 (Box 26)
  - Mar.25(L.R. Alderman) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Apr.14(Lewis Compton) (Box 26)
  - June 8(lzetta J. Miller (Box 26)
  - July 12(Fredericka Belknap),14 (Box 26)
  - Aug. 25 (Box 26)
  - 1941: July 2 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ely, Mrs. William H.J. & Family 1941: Nov.? F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Ely, Harvey & Mary 1941: Nov.? F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Enger, Arthur 1939: ?(to a group of people in NJ) F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Eryeian, Charles M. 1940: Oct.28 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - F (Box 26)
  - Farrington, Madeline E. (Secretary, Leonia Democratic Club) 1937: June 10,18,22 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Fernandez, Josephine 1935: Dec.2 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Fowler, George M.C. 1940: Oct.23 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1941: July 20 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1942: July Apr.17 (Box 26)
  - Frankel, Emil(Dir. Div. of Statistics Research, State of NJ, Dept. of Institutions & Agencies) 1936: Dec.l F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Frirsurs, Molly F. 1935: Dec.l F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - G (Box 26)
  - Gabbert, Verb Amber 1938: Dec.20 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1939: May 9 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sept.?(Robert W. Allan) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Gaines, Charlotte 1938: Sept.? F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1940: July 30 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Glennon, Ray 1941: July 5 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Grant, Anna 1937: Jan.11 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1941: July 22 F 9 (Box 26)
  - Green, Thomas V. 1938: June 5 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Greywacz, Kathryn B. 1938: Mar.11 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1941: Oct.23 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - H (Box 22)
  - Haas, Mervil E. 1938: Jan.3 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hague, Frank(Mayor, Jersey City, NJ) 1936: Dec.1(Madeline E. F 3 Farrington) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Dec.3(Frank S. Smith) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hall, John 1939: Feb.7 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1939: Feb.7 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hall, John 1939: Feb.? F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hamilton, Margaret Porch(Chm, Leonia Woman Forum. Democrat) •s 1935: Oct.22 (Robert W. Allan F 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Halley, Katharine 1941: Feb.9 May 20 July 1 Feb. 9. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Harlan, Ethel M. 1939: Sept.28 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1941: July 3 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Harris, Bernice 1938: Sept.15 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Higham, Justus C. 1941: Feb.24(Robert W. Allan) F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Hill, Lucie Edmondson 1940: Dec.1,4 F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Hill, Roscoe R.(Chief, The National Archives, Div. of Classification) 1936: Dec.16,16(Wm.H.J. Ely) F 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Hobby. Arthur S. 1938: Feb.7,14 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hogan, Leo P. 1938: Apr. 12 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Nov. 5 (Box 26)
  - Hooks, Maud Montgomery(D.A.R.) 1937: Feb.2 F 4. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Hopler, Kathleen G. 1939: Aug. 5 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Hutchinson, Viola L. 1933: Dec.15 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1937: Nov.12 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1938: Mar.14,14(Irene Fuhlbruegge) Dec.3,3(Henry G. Alsberg) F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1939: July Ronald G, Chessman F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1941: Apr.4,9 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - May ? (Box 26)
  - June 2(Wm DeBary) (Box 26)
  - June 30 (Box 26)
  - Aug.21 (Box 26)
  - 1942: Feb. 13 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1969: Aug.18 F 15 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - J (Box 22)
  - Jones, W.J. 1933: Nov.25 F 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - K (Box 22)
  - Katzenbach, III, Frank S. 1938: ? F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Kearns, W.A. 1937: July 23 F 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Keary, Thomas S. 1938: Sept.10 F 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Keating, Aneita 1941: (2)n. 1937: July 15 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - June,18 F4 (Box 26)
  - Kenney, tawara A. ±93o: D§c.3(Madeline O E. Farrington) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Kerr, Florence 1939: Jan.24 F 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Dec.25 (Box 26)
  - 1940: Dec.?(2) F 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 1941: Jan.14 F 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)